

Malang, East Java+62 812 8370 9830

Summary

My name is Bintang Ramadhan, you may call me Bram for short. I am currently a System Information Student at University of Brawijaya. Passionate at Software Engineering and a skilful Full-Stack Web Developer. I have been freelancing as a Web Developer over the past two years. I have developed and worked for up to 10 projects for web based software. The more I learn, the more I know that I know nothing. That being said, I will never stop learning and get more experiences up ahead.

Work experience

Head Of Web Manager

Dec 2020 - Present

TEDX UNIVERSITAS BRAWIJAYA 2021

Created TEDxUniversitasBrawijaya2021 Official Website.

https://www.tedxuniversitasbrawijaya.com/

Head Of Web Manager

MAY 2020 - DEC 2020

CREANOMIC 2020

Created Creanomic2020 Official Website. Created Livestream Channel for National Scope. Created Virtual Art Exhibition Performance.

http://creanomic.ub.ac.id/

Information Technology (IT) Staff

APR 2020 - OCT 2020

RAJABRAWIJAYA

Created RAJA Brawijaya Landing Page and RAJA APPs Front-end.

VICE HUMAN RESOURCES MANAGER

SEP 2019 - Present

HIMMASI

Created Three HIMMASI's Massive Events (SAMBA, MAKRAB, Study Excursive).

Education

Associate's Degree

2019 - Present

Univesity Of Brawijaya

Handled LPPM UB Official Docs and Admin Dashboard

Skills

ReactJS

VueJS							/_	
Laravel					 	7		
MongoDB			7_	7_	 7_		/_	
SQL					 	7_	/_	
NodeJS		7_	7_	7_	 7_		7	
PHP		7_	7_	7_	 7_	7_	7	
JavaScript							7	
CSS		7_					7_	
HTML								